Uzys SMI Merge Tool http://uzys.net
Uzys 통합 자막 생성기 http://uzys.net
한글자막 호랑나비완
피드백 http://swallowt.tistory.com
1963년 3월 21일
On march 21, 1963,
알카트라즈는 치솟는 유지비와
노후한 시설을 이유로
Alcatraz officially closed
due to rising costs
공식적으로 폐쇄되었다
and decrepit facilities.
그리고 모든 죄수들은
이감되었다한다...
All the prisoners were
transferred off the island...
하지만 실제로
일어난 일은...
Only, that's not
what happened.
전혀 달랐다
Not at all.
알카트라즈
1963년 3월 20일
이게 뭐야?
What the hell?
왜요?
What is it?
총 꺼내
Ready your weapon.
무슨 일입니까?
What's happening?
항상 간수 두명이
이감을 봐야해
Two guards...
Always meet the transfer.
깜빡했나보죠
Maybe they forgot.
여기 알카트라즈야
This is Alcatraz.
그런 실수
아무도 안해
No one forgets.
누구 있습니까?
Is anyone here?
따라오게
Follow me.
본부에 무전해서
Radio the station.
총출동 해달라 해
Tell them
to send everyone.
그날 밤 302명이
사라졌다
302 men
disappeared that night.
그리고 아무도 그들의
소식을 들을 수 없었다
They were never seen
or heard from again...
지금 까지는 말이다
Until now.
24시간 개인
감방에 수감됐습니다
They stayed in
their cells 24 hours a day.
수지?
Susie?
대체 어디간거야?
Where the hell is she?
이봐, 여기서 자면 안돼
Hey, buddy,
you can't sleep in here.
나가는데 2분 주지
You got two minutes
to get the hell outta here.
말씀드린대로
1963년 3월 21일
As I was saying,
on March 21, 1963,
알카트라즈는 치솟는
비용과...
Alcatraz officially closed
due to rising costs...
표좀 확인하겠습니다
Ticket, sir?
재미있게 보셨죠
Hope you had
a nice time on the rock.
알카트라즈
중앙 수감실.1960
Inside "B" and "C" head count.
- 내실 B, C 점호!
- 내실 C 제1열 14명입니다
- 14, inside "C".
- First tier.
내실 C 제2열
15명입니다
15, inside "C" second tier.
내실 B 제1열
14명입니다
14, inside "B" first tier.
문열어!
Rack 'em!
선 앞에 정렬
Toes on the line.
이동.이동.이동!
25. Move, move, move, move!
앞으로 가!
Let's go!
그렇겐 안되지
2024호
Not so fast, 2024.
수색해
Shake it down.
깨끗합니다, 틸러씨
It's clean, Mr. Tiller.
깨끗 좋아하네
Clean, my ass.
내 것 아닙니다
That's not mine.
독방 보내
Take him away.
오늘 면회날이잖아요
Today's visiting day.
넌 못가겠네
Not for you.
E.B.틸러
FBI 최고훈장을 받다
Tiller.
틸러
Alcatraz
Ep 1 - Pilot
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Alcatraz
Ep 1 - Pilot
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
안돼!
No!
- 매드슨!
- 어서!
Madsen!
Come on!
내 손 잡아!
Take my hand!
어서!
Come on!
좋아, 됐어
Okay, all right.
아!
Aah!
매드슨
Madsen.
매드슨 형사
Detective Madsen.
내말 듣고는 있었나?
You hear a word
I've been saying?
존경하는 반장님한테
그렇다고 뻥칠 수는 없죠
Lieutenant, I respect you
too much to say yes.
3개월째 혼자 일하잖나
You've been flying solo
for three months.
이젠 파트너 정할 때도 됐어
It's time to get you
partnered up again.
아 맞다
저 할일이 좀...
Um, I just remembered
that I have...
앉아
Sit.
넵
Yes, sir.
리버스는 어때
Let's start with rivers.
얼마전에 마약반 일
끝냈는데
Just coming off
a stint in vice.
리버스는 절
형사로도 안볼걸요
You know, I don't think rivers
knows I'm a detective here.
볼때마다 커피
심부름 시킨다구요
He's always asking me
to make him coffee.
홀리어는?
How about Hollier?
너무 굼떠요
Too slow.
- 파이배쉬는
- 너무 빠르고요
- Fiveash.
- Too fast.
- 킬은
- 너무 금발이잖아요
- Kheel.
- Too blond.
우리 하디 보이즈
같을 거에요
We'd look like
the Hardy boys.
이보게... 그 날 일은
다들 안타까워 하고 있어
Look...We all took
a loss that day.
하지만 자책은
이제 그만둬
But you gotta stop
blaming yourself.
자책안해요
I don't.
그친구 밀은 놈을
원망할뿐이에요
I blame the guy
that pushed him off the roof.
식별사진도
다 확인했고
We've been through
the mug shots.
단서란 단서는
다 살펴봤잖아
We followed every lead.
이젠 넘어갈 때가 됐어
It's time to move on.
매드슨
살인사건이야
Madsen,
we got a homicide.
네가 맡아
You're up.
음..
Um...
반장님 말이 맞아요
다들 괜찮죠
You're right.
Those are great choices.
음...
Um...
전 단지...
I just...
나도 아네
Yeah, I know.
하루만 더주세요
꼭 정할게요
Give me the day,
and I'll pick someone.
약속드립니다
I promise.
고마워요, 반장님
Thank you, lieutenant.
관뚜겅 반은 닫은
노인네를 누가 죽인거야
Who murders a guy
who's already got
one hip in the grave?
희생자는 이름은
일라이자 베일리 틸러
Victim's
Elijah Bailey Tiller.
E.B.로 통한답니다
Folks called him E.B.
78세고 이웃 말로는
문이 열려 있었다네요
78. Neighbor says
the door was open.
레베카
Rebecca,
희생자 있잖아...
연방쪽 사람였나봐요
the Vic... he was a fed.
좋아 쫓겨나기 전에
최대한 많이 챙겨둬
All right, let's get
all we can before we get tossed.
댁들은 여기서
일없어요
You're done here.
뭐라고요?
Excuse me?
희생자는 연방공무원이요
The victim was a federal agent.
- 우리가 맡습니다
- 누가 그래요?
- We're taking over.
- Says who?
내가 그럽니다
Says me.
당신이 누구신데?
And you are?
에머슨 하우저
Emerson Hauser.
이제 나가시지
Now, get out.
I don't leave a crime scene
직속상관의 명령없이
현장을 떠날 순 없습니다만
unless my immediate superior
orders me to.
됐죠, 이제 나가 놀아요
Okay, run along and play now.
싸가지 없어줘서
대단히 고맙네요
Thanks for being
a dick about it.
지미, 부탁 좀 할까?
Jimmy, do me a favor?
에머슨 하우저 좀
데이터 베이스에 돌려봐
Run Emerson Hauser
through the database.
어디서 온 놈인지
알아야겠어
I wanna know
where he came from.
뭐하려고요?
What are you gonna do?
잭 실베인
Jack Sylvane.
젠장
Damn it.
알카트라즈
Alcatraz.
희생자 이름이
E.B.틸러였네
Vic's name was E.B. Tiller.
부교도장?
Deputy warden?
흠, '디에고 소토'라
Hmm.
Diego Soto.
무슨 사연이신가?
What's your story?
에이, 에이
그런게 어딨어
Come on, come
on, that's not fair.
- 박사님, 정말 그렇게요?
- 쉬, 쉬, 쉬!
Doc, you really wanna do that?
Shh, shh, shh!
좋아 좋아 좋아
Come on, come on,
come on.
- 거기 간다
- 닥쳐
- There ya go.
- Shut up.
오!
Oh!
합체하는데 너무
신경 쓰시잖아요
You're too worried
about the double-ups, doc.
그냥 쏴도 돼요
You just gotta shoot.
합체는 꼭 해야해
You have to double up.
합체가 핵심이라고
Double-ups are key.
그러게요 합체도 안하고
어떻게 최고점을 찍겠어요
Yeah, the high
score's a pipe dream
without the double-up.
저는 팩맨을
더 좋아했어요
Of course, I'm more
partial to Pac-man,
아마 먹는걸
좋아해서 그랬나봐요
but maybe that's 'cause
I like to eat.
디에고 소토요
나랑 결혼합시다
Diego Soto.
Will you marry me?
디에고 소토 박사님?
Dr. Diego Soto?
보는 것보다는
훨씬 똑똑하다고요
I'm way smarter
than I look.
사법제도학하고
남북전쟁사에 학위 있으시죠
Phds in criminal justice
and civil war history.
알카트라즈 관련
책을 4권 쓰셨고요?
Four books on Alcatraz?
웬만한 사람보다는
한참 똑똑하신것 같은데요
I'd say you're way smarter
than we all look.
레베카 매드슨형사입니다
I'm detective
Rebecca Madsen.
사건에 도움주십사 해서요
I was hoping to borrow you
for a case.
이 두명 알아보시겠어요?
These two look familiar?
그래요
Yeah.
제임스 교도장하고
부교도장 틸러요
Warden James
and his deputy Tiller?
제임스는 오래전에
고인됐구요
James is long dead,
틸러는 아직
살아 있습니다
but Tiller,
he's still alive.
혹시 수감자중에서
You ever do any research
잭 실베인이란 자
조사해 보셨나요?
on an inmate
named Jack Sylvane?
실베인?
Sylvane?
운도 없는 녀석이었죠
That was one unlucky cat.
2차대전의
참전용사였는데
The guy was
a World War II vet.
식료품점을 털다
'더 락(알카트라즈 별칭)'에 갇혔죠
Got sent to the rock
for robbing a grocery store.
연방 범죄도 아닌데요?
How's that
a federal crime?
그래서 운없었다는 거에요
그 가게에서 우표를 팔았거든요
That's the unlucky part.
The store sold stamps.
우체국으로 간주됐군요
Which makes it
a post office.
가족 먹여살리려다
연방범죄자가 된거죠
And feeding your family
becomes a federal offense.
레븐워스에 보내졌다가
Sent him to leavenworth.
다른 수감자가
샤워중에 덮쳤는데
Another prisoner
got frisky in the shower.
잭이 그만 죽여버렸죠
Jack murders him.
다음 역은, "더 락"
Next stop, the rock.
근데
잭 실베인은 왜요?
So...Why all the interest
in Jack Sylvane?
E.B.틸러가 어제
살해됐어요
E.B. Tiller
was killed last night.
실베인 지문이
현장에서 나왔고요
Sylvane's prints
showed up at the scene.
미안하지만
말도 안되는데요
I'm sorry.
That's just not possible.
왜요?
Why not?
잭 실베인은
30년전에 죽었거든요
'Cause Jack Sylvane
died over 30 years ago.
알카트라즈, 독방- 1960년
- 좋아 2024호 일어나
Okay, 2024, on your feet.
가자
Let's go.
잘한다
Attaboy.
옳지
That's it.
내 아내에겐
뭐라 했습니까?
What did
you say to my wife?
어이쿠 이걸 어쩌나
Oh, would you look
at that?
내가 실수를 했네
I must have made
a mistake.
오늘은 레드가 나가는 날이지
It's red
getting sprung today.
네놈이 아니라
Not you.
뭐라도 좀 들지
You should really
eat something.
잊지마
여긴 알카트라즈야
Remember,
this is Alcatraz.
최악인가 싶으면
더심한일이 항상 생기지
Things can always
get worse.
라커룸 좀 씁시다
I need to use
the locker room.
회원 아니시면
8달러 내셔야 합니다
It's 8 bucks to enjoy
the facilities as a guest.
이봐요 잔돈 받아가요
Hey, you got
some change comin'.
저기요
Hey.
잔돈이랑 새 수건이요
Brought you your change
and a fresh towel.
베키!
Becky!
레이 삼촌
Uncle Ray.
어서오너라
Hiya, sweetie.
뭐 좀 줄까?
Get ya something?
잭 온 더 락스요
Jack on the rocks.
잭 온 더 락스라, 응?
Jack on the rocks, huh?
살인 사건 하나
도와주세요
I need your help
with a homicide.
알카트라즈 시절에요
일라이자 베일리 틸러요
Goes back to Alcatraz.
DB's Elijah Bailey Tiller.
누군가 드디어
EB를 해치웠구만
So...Somebody finally
nailed E.B.
누군지 아실줄 알았어요
좋은 생각 없으세요?
I knew you'd know him.
Any insights?
센 녀석이었어
Ball breaker, this guy.
악질이었지
Of the worst variety.
더 락에선 10년정도
일했을거야
Worked the rock
for about ten years.
내가 간수였을때
부교도장이었고
Deputy warden
when I was a guard.
교도소 폐쇄전에
나갔어
Got out before
she shut down.
레이 아쳐?
Ray Archer?
소토 박사님
이쪽은 레이삼촌이요
Dr. Soto.
This is my Uncle Ray.
영광입니다, 선생님
It's an honor, sir.
날 아시오?
You know me?
알다뿐이겠어요
연구를 했습죠
Know you?
I studied you.
제 만화책에 선생님을
본뜬 캐릭터도 있는걸요
I even named a character
after you in my comic.
레이 아처가 삼촌이에요?
Ray Archer's your Uncle?
그런 셈이죠
Sort of.
부모님 돌아가시고
저 키워주셨거든요
He raised me after
my parents died.
우리 할아버지도
간수셨어요
My grandfather
was a guard too.
성함은 토미 매드슨이셨고
여기 레이삼촌이랑 절친이셨어요
Tommy Madsen.
He and Ray were best friends.
거기서 만나셨죠
할아버지 얘기도 썼어요?
It's where they met.
You write about him?
그럼요
Sure.
뭐 한잔 할래요, 총각?
Get you a drink, son?
클럽 소다로 부탁해요
Club soda would be great.
집에서 찾았어요
Well, I found him
back at my place.
잭 실베인은 산 퀜틴으로
이감명령을 받았는데
Jack Sylvane's transfer order
to San Quentin,
이감일이 63년에
교도소 닫던 날이었죠
dated the day the Rock
was closed in '63,
- 누가 서명했나 보세요
- 로버트 케네디네요
-and look who signed it.
-Robert Kennedy.
그리고 여기 사망증명서
And here's Jack's
death certificate.
네
Okay.
어떻게 죽은 사람 지문이
범행현장에서 나왔을까요
So how's a dead man
dropping fingerprints
- at a murder scene?
- You think these are phonies?
가짜라고 보세요?
기억이 맞다면, 틸러는
연방쪽에 갔었을거야
Memory serves...Tiller
joined up with the feds.
연방공무원은
연방쪽에서 수사할텐데
Federal officer
gets a federal investigation.
이건 네 사건 아니잖아
안그래 베키?
This isn't your case,
is it, Becky?
- 아뇨, 하지만..
- 아닌건 아닌거다
-No, but...
- No, but nothing.
네 사건 아니면
그만두도록 해
If it's not your case,
stay out of it.
알카트라즈 일이에요
삼촌이 일했던...
This is about Alcatraz.
You worked...
젠장, 레베카
Damn it, Rebecca.
그냥 놔둬
Let it go.
제발 한번만이라도
그냥 넘어가라
For once in your life,
just...walk away.
우리 부모님은..
My folks...
진짜 진짜 똑똑하셨어요
Are really, really smart.
스탠포드에서 가르치셨죠
They teach at Stanford.
항상 저보고
이래라 저래라 하셨어요
And they're always
telling me what to do.
그런데..
But...
똑똑하다고 행복한건
아니더라고요
Smart doesn't always
make you happy.
그래서 대개는
부모님 말씀 잘 듣고나서
So mostly, I just
hear what they have to say...
정 반대로 행동했죠
And then I do the opposite.
전문가로서
어떻게 된 것 같아요?
You're the expert.
What do you think happened?
모르죠
I don't know.
하지만 지난번 방문했을때
But last time on the island,
어쩌다 서류랑 상자가
가득한 방에 들어갔는데
I stumbled across a room
that was full of files and boxes
봐서는 안되는
것들이 잔뜩이더라구요
and all sorts of stuff
I wasn't supposed to see.
33번 부두
첫배 괜찮죠?
Pier 33,
first boat out?
커피는 제가 가져갑죠
I'll bring the coffee.
샌 퀜틴 교도장과
이야기를 했는데요
So I spoke to the warden
at San Quentin.
실베인이 76년에
이감, 사망했다는군요
He confirms Sylvane's transfer
and death in '76.
하지만 형사님은 살아서
틸러를 죽였다고 보시고요
But you think he's alive
and that he killed Tiller.
모르겠어요
그냥 말이 안돼요
I don't know.
It just doesn't make sense.
실베인은 좀도둑이지
살인자가 아니잖아요
Sylvane was a thief,
not a killer.
만약 잭이 내내
살아 있었다면
So if Jack's been around
all this time,
왜 이제서야
틸러를 죽였을까요
why'd he wait so long
to kill Tiller?
대체 어디 있었던 걸까요?
Where the hell's he been?
여기는요?
Where are we now?
간수실이요
The barracks.
간수들이 가족들과
여기서 살았죠
The guards lived here
with their families.
애들이 이런데서
살았다니 상상이 안가요
I can't imagine
children living here.
매일 배타고
등교를 했더랬죠
They took the boat
to school every day.
스쿨버스보다는
훨씬 멋지잖아요
Way cooler than the bus.
여기에요
Here's the room.
잠겼네요
어쩌죠?
Still locked.
Any ideas?
경찰 보급품이 있죠
Department issue.
불좀요
Flashlight.
형사하기엔 좀
젊으신거 아니에요?
Aren't you kind of young
to be a detective?
네 그런 소리
많이 듣죠
Yeah. I get that a lot.
끝내주는 사연이
또 있겠죠
Bet you have a pretty cool
origin story.
경찰집안에서 컸어요
I was raised by a cop.
아버지가 사건파일을
가져오면 자기전에 읽곤했죠
He'd bring his cases home,
I'd read them before bed,
내 생각을 포스트잇에
적어 붙여놓곤했어요
put post-its where
I thought he should look.
실제로 몇몇은
도움이 되기도 했구요
I actually helped him
solve a few cases.
멋지군요
Nice.
이감을 했다면서
왜 재소자 파일만 남았을까요
How come the inmate files
weren't transferred
with the inmates?
이런 세상에!
여기좀 봐요
Holy crap!
You gotta come see this.
- 이건...
- 전부 다 있어요
- This is...
- Everything!
다 재소자 물건이에요
It's all their stuff.
무장중인
경찰이다!
SFPD!
I'm armed.
그건 대체 뭐에요?
What the hell is that?
이러면 곤란해
This is a mistake.
저 여자가 우릴
찾아냈잖아요
She found us,
그 자를 잡을때까지
멈추지 않을거에요
and she won't stop
until she finds him.
당신한텐 저여자가
필요해요, 에머슨
You need her, Emerson.
좋아, 깨셨군
Good. You're awake.
매드슨 형사
Detective Madsen...
알카트라즈에 잘오셨소
Welcome to Alcatraz.
음..
Mm...
머리야
My head.
우리 어디에요?
Where are we?
알카트라즈요
Alcatraz.
- Looks good.
- Yep.
인테리어가 많이
바뀌었네요
They've done
some redecorating.
소토 박사
난 하우저요
Dr. Soto, I'm Hauser.
당신 책을 읽었죠
I read your books.
우리한테..
가스 쏘신거에요?
Um, did you...gas us?
침입자 대응규칙이
엄격해서요
We have strict protocols
for intruders here.
전 루시 베너지에요
I'm Lucy Banerjee.
꽤 유능하시네요
매드슨 형사님
You're quite resourceful,
detective Madsen.
현장에서 사진을
들고가는건
Lifting the photo
from the crime scene
대범하고
효과적이었어요
was not only bold
but effective.
사진 돌려주시오
I'll need that back.
에머슨 하우저 왜
당신기록이
Emerson Hauser,
you wanna tell me why
FBI에 없는지 설명해봐요
there's no record of you
working for the FBI?
난 특수부서를 맡고있소
I run a special division
in charge of criminals
정부의 특별한 관심을 받고있는
범죄자들을 취급하지
who hold a particular allure
for our government.
그딴 헛소리
믿으란건 아니죠?
You know I don't believe
a word of that, right?
그래서..
So...
비밀기지를...
You built the bat cave...
알카트라즈 지하에
지었군요
Underneath Alcatraz.
근데 뭐하러요?
But why would you do that?
저 노인은 누구죠?
Who's the old guy?
저 사진은 컴퓨터로
추정한 거에요
That is a
computer-generated simulation
잭 실베인의 현재
외모였어야 했죠
of what Jack Sylvane
should look like today.
였어야했다?
Should?
루씨, 그린가 보안
카메라 돌려봐요
Lucy, run the green street
surveillance.
교통 카메라가
지난밤 잡았어요
Traffic cam
caught this last night.
노인이 희생자 틸러고
The older gentleman
is our victim... E.B. Tiller,
그리고 소개합니다
and meet...
잭 실베인
Jack Sylvane.
85세의 젊은이죠
85 years young.
뭐요?저사람이?
What? That's him?
소토 박사님?
Dr. Soto?
맞아요
It's him.
잭 실베인은 1963년
알카트라즈에서 실종됐어요
Jack Sylvane disappeared
from Alcatraz in 1963.
그게 무슨 소리에요?
탈옥말인가요?
What does that mean,
he escaped?
아무도 알카트라즈에선
탈옥못해요
No one ever escaped
Alcatraz.
당연히 저렇게
똑같은 사람도...
Not to mention,
the guy looks exactly the same,
잘 알고 있겠지만...
which, if you're keeping
score at home,
존재할 수 없구요
isn't possible.
그럼 산 퀜틴 이감은
위장이었군요
So the San Quentin transfer
was bogus.
사망증명도
그렇구요
As was
the death certificate.
그래도 전혀 안 늙은건
설명이 안되는데요
That still doesn't explain
why he hasn't aged.
그래, 그렇죠
No, it doesn't.
네?
Yes?
무슨 일이에요
What's going on?
경찰이 죄수복을
찾았답니다
Local PD found a uniform
at a crime scene.
알카트라즈 보급품이요
Alcatraz issue.
있죠
사진은 돌려드리죠
Tell you what...
I'll give you your prints back
저도 데려가 주신다면요
if you let me come
with you.
왜요?
Why?
가스 먹였으니 그정돈
해줘야 하는거 잖아요?
Because you gassed me,
and now you owe me one.
도시락통 잘
챙겨 오시오
Don't forget
your lunchbox.
가요, 박사님
Yeah.
Let's go, doc.
갑니다요!
Coming!
어디 계속 해봐
Keep at it.
피를 다뽑을 셈이구만
You'll owe me
a transfusion.
독방에 한달 쳐박혔으면
You'd think a month
in the hole
입조심을 하는 법을
좀 배웠어야 하는데말이야
would teach you
not to run your mouth.
그냥 하는 소리야..
멀쩡한 놈한테
Just saying...
That's a lotta blood
무슨 피를 그리
많이 뽑냐구요
from a guy
who ain't sick.
어이구, 의사 선생님신걸
못알아 봤네요
Oh, I didn't know there was
another doctor among us.
실베인 선생님한테
청진기갖다 드리세요
Fetch me a stethoscope
for Dr. Sylvane here.
부탁하나하자, 잭
Do me a favor, Jack.
의학적이건 뭐건
당신 소견은
Keep your opinions,
medical or otherwise,
혼자만 간직하는게
좋을거야
to your godforsaken self.
얼마나 뽑아갔수?
So how many
they take from you?
뭐라구요?
'Scuse me?
따뜻하고 빨간
피주머니요
Vials of warm red blood?
그게 당신이랑
무슨 상관이야?
What the hell
do you care?
저 아랫동네에 비하면
이정돈 아무것도 아냐
This place is nothing
compared to downstairs.
안그래도 면회날에
거기 집어 넣더군
Sent me out on visiting day.
독방 이야기가 아니야
I'm not talking about
the hole.
독방 그 아래를
말하는 것이지
I'm talking about
below the hole.
아내 볼 기회를 놓쳤어
I missed seeing my wife.
날 믿어
그게 나아
Trust me,
you're better off.
넌 대체 뭔데?
Who the hell are you?
너랑 같지
The same as you.
번호로 불리는 인간
A number.
2002호
2002.
그래...
Yeah, well...
2002호 난 너 안믿어
2002, I don't trust you.
나아질 리가 없다고
And I ain't better off.
내말 잘들어
You listen to me.
끔찍한 일이 일어날거야
Something terrible's
gonna happen here.
잭의 수감번호네요
2024.
That's Jack's number.
이자가 공격했소?
Is this the man
who attacked you?
네 그 개자식이요
Yeah.
That's the son of a bitch.
락커 열쇠를
주셨나요?
Did you give him
a locker key?
아뇨 달라고
안하더라구요
No. He never asked.
로비의 카메라는
작동하구요?
And is the video camera
in the lobby working?
농담하세요?
You kidding me?
여기 물건들 망가진지
수십년은 됐을거에요
Nothing's worked here
since like 1975.
여기요
Here.
591 NPQN.
- 차번호네요
- 택시번호에요
- You got a plate number.
- It's the cab he took off in.
조회해볼게요
I'll have SFPD run it.
천천히 돌아서!
Turn around slow!
당장!
Do it now!
손 보이게 꺼내!
손 꺼내라고!
Show me your hands.
I said show me your hands!
바클리 플린이요?
Are you Barclay Flynn?
당신 찾아왔지
I'm here for you.
- 아!
- 금고 열어
- Aah!
- Open the safe.
알았어요
Okay.
See?
여기요
다가져가세요
Here. You can have
anything you want.
주머니 내놔
Gimme the bag.
무슨 주머니요?
What bag?
거기 작은 주머니
The soft black bag.
여기 가져가요
Here, take it.
Take it.
그게다에요?
그거 가지러 왔어요?
That's it?
That's what you came for?
이런 세상에
Oh, my God.
- 박동은 있어요
- 이쪽은 없네
- I got a pulse.
- This one's gone.
경관이 당했다
반복한다 경관이 당했다
Officer down.
I repeat... office down.
지원및 응급차량
바란다
We need backup and a bus.
같이 있어요
Stay with him.
놓쳤어요
I lost him.
이자는 바클리 플린이요
His name is Barclay Flynn.
실베인이랑은
무슨 관계입니까?
So what's this guy's
connection to Sylvane?
무슨 관계가
있어야 하는 거요?
Why assume
there has to be one?
어이구, 바보같이
동기를 찾고있네요
Silly me,
looking for motive.
잭 실베인이 플린을
몰랐다 하더라도
Even if Jack Sylvane
didn't know Flynn,
어딘가엔 플린이 죽길
바라는 이들이 있었을 겁니다
it doesn't mean there weren't
people who wanted him dead.
지금 암시하시는게...
So...you're implying
실베인이 누군가에게
이용을 당해서
that Sylvane's
being used by someone,
이런짓을 한다는 건가요?
that he was told to do this.
암시같은거 안해
생각한대로 말할뿐이오
I don't think
I was implying it.
I thought
I was saying it.
뭐 알아냈어요?
What have you got?
있죠
잭슨 아내가 재혼했는데
Listen,
Jack's wife remarried.
그냥 다른 사람이랑
한게 아니에요
Only get this...
Wasn't just some guy.
잭의 동생과
재혼을 했어요
She married Jack's brother.
부인은 아직 살아있어요?
She's still alive?
잭이 찾아갈 수 있잖아요
Jack could go
looking for her.
죽었습니다
She's dead.
하지만 동생은
살아있어요
But his brother,
he's still alive.
하지만 잭이 만약
그걸 안다면...
And if Jack knows that...
- 그래요, 다음 목표겠죠
- 우오
- Right. He could be next.
- Whoa.
저 엘리옷 네스는 어쩌구요?
What about Eliot Ness?
우리끼리가면
열받아 하지 않을까요?
Won't he be pissed
if we leave without him?
잭을 찾아서
무슨 일인지 알아내야해요
I wanna find Jack.
I wanna know what happened.
저 자가 말해줄리
없으니까요
And he's never
gonna tell us.
그래서..같이 하는 거죠?
So...are you with me?
당연하죠
All the way.
무슨 일이시죠?
Hi. Can I help you?
전 잭인데
어...
I'm Jack.
Uh...
앨런 실베인을
찾고 있습니다만?
I'm looking for
Alan Sylvane?
아 제가 아들입니다
I'm Alan junior.
I'm his son.
제 아버님과
친구셨어요
Uh...our dads
were friends.
들어오세요
Come on in.
모셔올게요
I'll get dad.
꽃들은 어때?
How are your flowers?
음..
Um...
장미는 잘크고
The roses, they grow,
but...
튤립은 시들어 가
The tulips are dying.
안됐네
I'm sorry to hear that.
지난달엔
Last month I come
and...
당신 아팠다고?
They say you are ill?
지금은 괜찮아
I'm good now.
걱정했어
I'm worried.
물어볼 사람이 있어야지
And...there is no one
I can ask.
미안해
I'm sorry about that.
당신 동생 앨런이
안부 전하래
Your brother, uh, Alan,
says hello.
걔가 잘 돌봐주고 있어?
He looking out for you?
나 있지..
I must, um...
뭐좀 물어볼게 있어
Ask you for something.
그래 뭐든지
필요한거 말해
- Yeah, anything.
- Anything you need.
안돼
Oh, no.
제발, 날 보내줘
Oh, please,
you must let me go.
나한테 이러지마, 소냐
Please don't do this,
Sonya.
- 그래야해
- 제발 이러지마
- I have to.
- Please don't do this.
제발..나 좀
보내줘
Please...you must
let me go.
- 이럴수 없어
- 이혼 해줘
- Don't do this.
- Give me a divorce.
안돼, 안돼
No. No. No. No.
재키, 난 못하겠어
Jackie, I can't do this.
- 재키
- 안돼
-Jackie...
- No!
그만해, 잭
Ah!
That's it, Jack.
면회끝이다
You're done.
감방으로 돌아가, 잭
Back to your cell, Jack!
저희 어머니에요
That's my mom.
4년전 돌아가셨죠
She died four years ago.
눈이 닯았네요
You have her eyes.
안녕, 앨런
Hello, Alan.
어떻게?
How?
전혀 안변했네
You look the same.
넌 늙었네
You got old.
네가 죽었다고 했어
They told me
you died.
네 무덤에 내가
흙도 뿌렸다고
I threw dirt
on your coffin.
고통스러워했어?
Did she suffer?
암이었어
She got cancer.
고통스러웠지
She suffered.
무슨일이 일어난거야, 재키
What happened to you,
Jackie?
무슨일이겠어..
What happened was...
동생이 내 아내와
결혼을 해버렸는데
My brother married my wife.
그 뒤에 일어난
다른일들이야..
And nothing
that came after that...
쥐뿔만큼도 중요하지않아
Matters worth a damn.
경찰이다!
Police!
- 아버지를 데려갔어요
- 누가요?
- He took my dad.
- Who did?
이름이 잭이라 했어요
He said his name
was Jack.
어디로 간다고 했나요?
He say where
he was going?
자기 부인을
찾으러 간댔어요
Said he wanted to find
his wife.
괜찮아, 소냐
It's okay, Sonya.
당신이 한일
What you did.
내 마음속엔..
In my heart...
당신 사랑하는
마음만 있으니까
There's only love for you.
돌아서 잭
Turn around, Jack.
내가 당신 알던가?
Do I know you?
아니 모르지
No, you don't.
자 총을 건네줘
Now, give me your gun,
그럼 머리통 날리진
않을테니까
and I won't blow
your brains out.
총 건네줘, 잭
Gimme the gun, Jack.
다른 사람 해치고
싶지 않잖아
You don't want to hurt
anyone else.
난 사람들을 해쳤어
I hurt people.
가증스러워
틸러를 죽였어
I killed Tiller
out of hate.
다른 사람..플린은?
And the other guy... Flynn?
그사람은 왜 죽였지?
Why'd you kill him?
시키는대로 했을뿐이야
I only did
what they told me.
누가 뭘시켰는데?
What who told you?
잭
Jack.
누가 뭘 시킨거냐고?
What who to you?
그동안 어딨었어?
Where have you been?
당신한테 무슨 일이
일어났던거야, 잭?
What happened
to you, Jack?
날 쏴
Shoot me.
싫어
No.
잭, 총 내려놔!
Jack, put down the gun!
내려놓고
무릎꿇어!
Do it!
Get on your knees!
여기가 내가
있을 곳이야
This is where I belong!
이봐! 멈춰!
Hey! Ho! Stop!
무슨 일이 일어난
건지 말해봐, 잭
Tell me what happened
to you, Jack.
응?어떻게 된거야?
Huh? What happened?
내가 데려가지
I'll take it
from here.
당신 할만큼 했어
You've done enough
on your own.
날 죽였어야했어
You should have
killed me.
약속한대로
지문 한 점이요
One fingerprint,
as promised.
잭은 어떻게 됐어요?
So what happened
to Jack?
수감됐소
He's in prison.
끝내주는 새로운 신분으로
멋진 무기징역을 받았죠
A spanking new identity
and a nice long life sentence.
동생은요?
What about his brother?
문제될 것 없을 거요
Oh, he won't be a problem.
"문제될 것 없다"?
"He won't be a problem"?
플린건 알아봤는데요
I looked into this Flynn.
잭 실베인이나 알카트라즈와는
전혀 관계가 없더군요
No ties to Jack Sylvane
or Alcatraz.
바클리 플린 건은
잊으시오
Forget about Barclay Flynn.
다음 희생자 걱정을
해야하니까
We need to worry about
our next victim.
"다음 희생자"요?
"Our next victim"?
잭 실베인은
시작일 뿐이오
Jack Sylvane
was just the beginning.
이런일 있을줄
알고 있었군요
You knew this was
gonna happen.
그래서 여기 있었던거야
이런일 대비하려고
That's why you're here.
You've been waiting for this.
아주 오래 오래 기다렸지
A very, very long time.
따라와요
Come with me.
63년도를 소개하지
Meet the '63s.
오른쪽 256명은 죄수
256 prisoners on the right.
왼쪽 46명은 교도관이오
46 guards on the left.
1963년 3월 21일
On March 21, 1963,
알카트라즈는 치솟는 유지비와
노후한 시설을 이유로
Alcatraz officially closed
due to rising costs
공식적으로 폐쇄됐소
and decrepit facilities.
그리고 모든 죄수들은
이감되었다했지만
All the prisoners
were transferred
off the island.
하지만 실제로
일어난 일은...
Only,
that's not what happened.
전혀 달랐소
Not at all.
본부에 무전해서
Radio the station.
총출동 해달라 해
Tell them
to send everyone.
어이
Kid.
여기 사람들이
다 어디로 갔는지
I don't know where
these men went
무슨 일인진 몰라도
우린 할일을 해야해
or what happened to them,
but we need to do our job.
알아들었나?
You understand me?
자네 이름이 뭔가?
What's your name?
하우저입니다
Hauser.
에머슨 하우저
Emerson Hauser.
이 나라에 있었던
최악의 범죄자들이
The worst criminals
this country has ever known
돌아올 것이네
are coming back.
우리 터전으로
돌아오는 거지
They're coming back
to our streets,
그리고 누구도 그놈들을
찾아 낼 수 없을거야
and no one's gonna be able
to find them
왜냐면 존재하지
않는 인간들이거든
because they don't exist.
2002호
2002.
할아버지 교도관이 아니셨잖아
수감자였어
My grandfather wasn't a guard.
He was an inmate.
안돼!
No!
이 자야
That's him.
이 자가 내 파트너를
죽였어요
He killed my partner.
다 알고 있었죠
You knew this.
내가 이일 맡기를
내내 기다리셨군
You wanted me in on this
all along.
오, 아냐
잘못 알고 있어
Oh, no.
You've got that wrong.
자네는 너무 어리고
너무 성급해
You're too young.
You're too impetuous.
여기 남아서
저자를 잡고 싶다면
If you want to stay
and find him,
매일 매일
증명해야 할거야
you'll have to prove
to me every day
여기 있을 자격이
있는지 말이야
that you deserve
to be here.
머리 터질 것같은
사람 또 없어요?
Is anyone else's head
exploding right now?
나도 껴줘요
I want in.
자네 전근 명령서야
Your transfer orders.
어려운 일일거야
누구도 알아선 안되네
It'll be difficult for you.
No one can know.
레이 아처는 물론
어떤 친구도 안돼
Not Ray Archer,
not your friends.
누구도 안돼
No one.
만약 알게되면
If they found out,
아주 위험해질거야
it would be very,
very dangerous.
파트너가 필요해요
I'm gonna need a partner.
뭐, 저 사람?
What, him?
나요?
Me?
파트너를?
Partner?
네!
당연하죠!
Yes!
Of course yes!
잘됐네
Good.
잘됐어
자네 죽이고 싶지
않았거든
Wouldn't want to have
to kill you.
그래서 이 63년 인간들을
찾아야 한다 이거죠
So we have to find
these '63s.
그것 이상이야
More than that...
누가 그들을 데려 간건지
알아내야 하네
We need to find
who took them.
당신 알아
I know you.
그게 정말이라면
Well, if that's true,
몰랐던 사실이군
it's news to me.
집에 잘왔네, 잭
Welcome home, Jack.
날 곤란하게는
안할테지?
You're not gonna give me
a hard time, are you?
E.B.틸러는 내 친구였어
E.B. Tiller was my friend.
감방에 집어 넣어
Take him to his cell.
걱정하지마, 잭
Not to worry, Jack.
혼자있는 시간은
길지 않을거야
You won't be lonesome long.
Sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
한글자막 호랑나비완
피드백 http://swallowt.tistory.com